[
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XXL",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "American Indian or Alaskan Native | Asian or Asian-American | Pacific Islander | Black or African-American | Hispanic | White / Caucasian | Multiracial | Prefer not to answer | Other",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "All nuts | Peanuts | Tree nuts | Fish | Shellfish | Gluten | Soy | Eggs | Dairy | None | Other",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian | Vegan | Kosher | Halal | Gluten-free | Dairy-free | None | Other",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I need clarification on the difference",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "LAZAR.GOV",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I SWEEP THE DUCKS OFF OF OUR BENCHES",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "ONCE I BROKE INTO ONE AND STOLE THE FOOD",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "ONE PERSON WAS WHEREING DUMB LADDERHOSEN AND I JUDGES THEM",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I SNEAK UP BEHIND THEM AND YELL IN THEIR EARS THEN RUN AWAY",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "DUCK POOP SWEEPING",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Flyers/Posters | MLH website | Friends | Parents | Lick-Wilmerding website | A school newspaper | Teachers or school administrators | Student leaders | Hyphen-Hacks social media | MLH social media | Other",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "ANYTHING WITH CARBON",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "DOES IT HAVE CARBON??? THEN I CAN'T eat it!",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "LAZER DUCK EATER",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I STOLE FOOD FROM YOUR LAST HACKATHON",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2016-02-05",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T04:42:42Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-15T06:16:09Z",
    "email": "hyphenhackslw@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1205259873",
    "name": "DILBERT WOOILBERt",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "951458916",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {
        "home": {
          "address_1": "755 Ocean Ave",
          "city": "San Francisco",
          "country": "US",
          "postal_code": "94112",
          "region": "CA"
        }
      },
      "age": 3,
      "birth_date": "2016-02-05",
      "cell_phone": "5104092752",
      "email": "hyphenhackslw@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "DILBERT",
      "gender": "other",
      "last_name": "WOOILBERt",
      "name": "DILBERT WOOILBERt"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1205259873/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "American Indian or Alaskan Native | Asian or Asian-American | Pacific Islander | Black or African-American | Hispanic | White / Caucasian | Multiracial | Prefer not to answer | Other",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Gluten | None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Kosher | Gluten-free",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I need clarification on the difference",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "123455",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "123455",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "123455",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "123455",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "123455",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "123455",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website | Friends | Teachers or school administrators",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "asdf",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2015-04-05",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T04:49:41Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-15T06:32:24Z",
    "email": "hyphenhackslw@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1205265081",
    "name": "Hyphen Hacks",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "951462473",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {
        "home": {
          "address_1": "755 Ocean Ave",
          "city": "San Francisco",
          "country": "US",
          "postal_code": "94112",
          "region": "CA"
        }
      },
      "age": 4,
      "birth_date": "2015-04-05",
      "cell_phone": "123455",
      "email": "hyphenhackslw@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Hyphen",
      "gender": "other",
      "last_name": "Hacks",
      "name": "Hyphen Hacks"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1205265081/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "age": 19,
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "JOHN\"S DOGS EMPORIUM",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XS",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "American Indian or Alaskan Native | Asian or Asian-American | Pacific Islander | Black or African-American | Hispanic | White / Caucasian | Multiracial | Prefer not to answer | Other",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Fish | Gluten | None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian | Kosher | Gluten-free",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A LOT",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "BECAUSE OF FOOOOD",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I HATE COMPUTErs AND TECH",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge?",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Educational Background",
        "question_id": "23623037",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position in the tech industry?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Flyers/Posters | MLH website | Friends | Parents | Lick-Wilmerding website | A school newspaper | Teachers or school administrators | Student leaders | Hyphen-Hacks social media | MLH social media",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "HAHAHAH",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2000-04-10",
    "changed": "2019-05-16T03:18:37Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-16T03:18:36Z",
    "email": "bib@bib.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": "male",
    "id": "1206260089",
    "name": "BOB LARRY",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "952085618",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {
        "home": {
          "address_1": "755 Ocean Ave",
          "city": "San Francisco",
          "country": "US",
          "postal_code": "94603",
          "region": "CA"
        }
      },
      "age": 19,
      "birth_date": "2000-04-10",
      "cell_phone": "39393939",
      "email": "bib@bib.com",
      "first_name": "BOB",
      "gender": "male",
      "last_name": "LARRY",
      "name": "BOB LARRY"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1206260089/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1206260089",
    "waiverMessage": "U suck",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "test@test.com",
      "name": "test@test.com"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1557978672927
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2023",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hyphen High Hacks",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XL",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Prefer not to answer",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "let me in\r\nLET ME IIIINNNNNNN",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "i helped run this little event you might have heard of called Hyphen-Hacks",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Ronan told me to sign myself up",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2019-01-01",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T04:57:32Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-16T04:54:01Z",
    "email": "hyphenhackslw@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1206304073",
    "name": "Hyphen Hacks",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "952111966",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {
        "home": {
          "address_1": "755 Ocean Ave.",
          "city": "San Francisco",
          "country": "US",
          "postal_code": "94112",
          "region": "CA"
        }
      },
      "age": 0,
      "birth_date": "2019-01-01",
      "cell_phone": "4153334021",
      "email": "hyphenhackslw@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Hyphen",
      "gender": "other",
      "last_name": "Hacks",
      "name": "Hyphen Hacks"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1206304073/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentor",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Stomprocket Inc",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Owner",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have been to Hyphen-Hacks as a child",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I teach knfie throwing, this can't be too different right?",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I throw bannan's at them",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I know how to sleep really well",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Flyers/Posters | MLH website | Lick-Wilmerding website | A school newspaper | Teachers or school administrators | Student leaders | MLH social media",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-02-08",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T05:06:49Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-21T04:38:25Z",
    "email": "rsf.sho@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1210468220",
    "name": "Ronan Furuta",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "954637283",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-02-08",
      "cell_phone": "5104092752",
      "email": "rsf.sho@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Ronan",
      "last_name": "Furuta",
      "name": "Ronan Furuta"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1210468220/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "All nuts | Tree nuts",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegan | Kosher",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentor",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "nope",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "LIES",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "HAHAH ur dunb",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "nop",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "nop",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would like to borrow a laptop for this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1905-06-04",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T05:04:38Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-22T04:10:11Z",
    "email": "rsf.sho@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1211473407",
    "name": "Gorbid SALDJH",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "955270860",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1905-06-04",
      "cell_phone": "5105308462",
      "email": "rsf.sho@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Gorbid",
      "last_name": "SALDJH",
      "name": "Gorbid SALDJH"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1211473407/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "All nuts | None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegan | Kosher",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentor",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "WORK PLEASE",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "WORK PLEASE",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "WORK PLEASE",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "WORK PLEASE",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "WORK PLEASE",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "WORK PLEASE",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends | I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2000-02-04",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T04:35:13Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-22T04:35:13Z",
    "email": "rsf.sho@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1211483296",
    "name": "WORK PLEASE WORK PLEASE",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "955277068",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2000-02-04",
      "cell_phone": "5104092752",
      "email": "rsf.sho@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "WORK PLEASE",
      "last_name": "WORK PLEASE",
      "name": "WORK PLEASE WORK PLEASE"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1211483296/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1211483296",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "kaya.erol@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Kaya Erol"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1558499806148
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XXL",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "All nuts",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Gluten-free",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Judge",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "ceo/epic fortnite gamer",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "i once ate a clam",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "snej ",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "jsjrbfb",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "dhebebdb",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Flyers/Posters",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1924-04-06",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T05:30:04Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-22T05:30:04Z",
    "email": "alexander_sherstnev@branson.org",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1211501940",
    "name": "yyggh f",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "955289145",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1924-04-06",
      "cell_phone": "111111181815646",
      "email": "alexander_sherstnev@branson.org",
      "first_name": "yyggh",
      "last_name": "f",
      "name": "yyggh f"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1211501940/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1211501940",
    "waiverMessage": "This is a terrible waiver and it somehow broke our system",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ronan.furuta@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ronan Furuta"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 3,
    "waiverUploaded": 1558503136239
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XL",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentor",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "slkdjf",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "sdlfkjsdf",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "sldkfj",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "sdlkfjsd",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "sdlkfjsldkf",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "sdfsdf",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Lick-Wilmerding website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1924-10-16",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T05:38:13Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-22T05:38:13Z",
    "email": "benjamin.j.grant@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1211504487",
    "name": "skfjdlkf sdlkfj",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "955290799",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1924-10-16",
      "cell_phone": "4159649627",
      "email": "benjamin.j.grant@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "skfjdlkf",
      "last_name": "sdlkfj",
      "name": "skfjdlkf sdlkfj"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1211504487/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1211504487",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "benjamin.j.grant@gmail.com",
      "name": "Ben Grant"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1558503541612
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XXL",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "All nuts",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Judge",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Funco",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Car",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Three",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "ham",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "tea",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "kite",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would like to borrow a laptop for this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Flyers/Posters",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1900-12-31",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T13:53:20Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-22T13:53:20Z",
    "email": "jkfuruta@protonmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1211761285",
    "name": "joey joey foo foo",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "955461124",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1900-12-31",
      "cell_phone": "555-555-5555",
      "email": "jkfuruta@protonmail.com",
      "first_name": "joey joey",
      "last_name": "foo foo",
      "name": "joey joey foo foo"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1211761285/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XXL",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Gluten-free",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentor",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hi",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Test",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "R",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "R",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "R",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "R",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Lick-Wilmerding website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1981-06-17",
    "changed": "2019-05-22T15:17:37Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-22T15:17:37Z",
    "email": "ketanhoey2@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1211850910",
    "name": "Ketan Hoey",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "955517446",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1981-06-17",
      "cell_phone": "6502693353",
      "email": "ketanhoey2@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Ketan",
      "last_name": "Hoey",
      "name": "Ketan Hoey"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1211850910/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1211850910",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ronan.furuta@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ronan Furuta"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1558539022642
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentor",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "SFUSD",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "CS Teacher",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentored HH last year",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentored HH last year",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "13 years as a math & CS teacher k-12",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Engineering, design & development, facilitation and encouragement.",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would like to borrow a laptop for this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1971-06-24",
    "changed": "2019-05-26T12:41:19Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-26T12:41:19Z",
    "email": "jacobsonj1@sfusd.edu",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1215245292",
    "name": "Jonathan Jacobson",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "957547957",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1971-06-24",
      "cell_phone": "5085230244",
      "email": "jacobsonj1@sfusd.edu",
      "first_name": "Jonathan",
      "last_name": "Jacobson",
      "name": "Jonathan Jacobson"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1215245292/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XS",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "All nuts | Peanuts | Dairy",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Halal",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Judge",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "asd",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "and",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "asd",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "asd",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "asd",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "asd",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would like to borrow a laptop for this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1911-02-04",
    "changed": "2019-05-29T17:58:54Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-05-29T17:58:54Z",
    "email": "rsf.sho@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1217866841",
    "name": "Blob Borb",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "959150379",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1911-02-04",
      "cell_phone": "5105308462",
      "email": "rsf.sho@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Blob",
      "last_name": "Borb",
      "name": "Blob Borb"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1217866841/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1217866841",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ronan.furuta@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ronan Furuta"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1559168591543
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Lick-Wilmerding High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Prefer not to answer",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Prefer not to say",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegan",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I want to go",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1908-09-11",
    "changed": "2019-06-28T19:08:05Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-06-28T19:08:05Z",
    "email": "ben.grant@hyphen-hacks.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Prefer not to say",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1244184459",
    "name": "test applicant",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "974964440",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1908-09-11",
      "cell_phone": "1234567890",
      "email": "ben.grant@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "first_name": "test",
      "last_name": "applicant",
      "name": "test applicant"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1244184459/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1244184459",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ben.grant@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ben Grant"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1561749034806
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentor",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Startup",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Founder",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Participated in LAUNCH hackathon and organized internal hackathons while at Findery.",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentored co-workers to find right-sized projects for internal hackathons at Findery.",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Volunteered as a TA in AP Computer Science Principles at Mission High School during the 2017-2018 school year.",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "React, React Native, golang, AWS, API design, networking.",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Student leaders",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1977-01-17",
    "changed": "2019-06-30T04:32:01Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-06-30T04:32:01Z",
    "email": "jedlau@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1245150950",
    "name": "Jed Lau",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "975508672",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1977-01-17",
      "cell_phone": "4154126055",
      "email": "jedlau@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Jed",
      "last_name": "Lau",
      "name": "Jed Lau"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1245150950/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Washington High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "To gain experience and learn.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have learned a bit in some college classes.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-02-16",
    "changed": "2019-06-30T06:30:43Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-06-30T06:30:43Z",
    "email": "ajvel777@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1245176185",
    "name": "Ajay Vellayapan",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "975523051",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-02-16",
      "cell_phone": "5103665836",
      "email": "ajvel777@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Ajay",
      "last_name": "Vellayapan",
      "name": "Ajay Vellayapan"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1245176185/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "University High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American | White / Caucasian | Multiracial",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Female",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I went last year and hadn’t a blast. Now that I’m a year older and more experienced in coding, I want to keep expanding my knowledge, collaborate and share what I know with more cool people, and overall keep pushing the limits of what I can do. ",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No formal computer science, but I took a practical programming class in Python the past year and would consider myself pretty proficient in Python. I’ve been to one hackathon (HyphenHacks last year). ",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Teachers or school administrators | I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-03-06",
    "changed": "2019-07-02T22:23:01Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-02T22:23:01Z",
    "email": "trholdridge@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Female",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247311676",
    "name": "Tulasi Holdridge",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976787270",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-03-06",
      "cell_phone": "4159392191",
      "email": "trholdridge@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Tulasi",
      "last_name": "Holdridge",
      "name": "Tulasi Holdridge"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247311676/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2021",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "College of San Mateo",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I want to further my programming skills, add something innovative to my resume, and meet new, like-minded people. ",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have attended multiple hackathons in the past, and have won only two or three. My computer science experience mostly comes from courses I have taken, which range from SQL to JavaScript. ",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Found on Eventbrite",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2003-10-22",
    "changed": "2019-07-02T22:44:03Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-02T22:44:03Z",
    "email": "jaygupt1973@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247326020",
    "name": "Jay Gupta",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976795917",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2003-10-22",
      "cell_phone": "6505152937",
      "email": "jaygupt1973@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Jay",
      "last_name": "Gupta",
      "name": "Jay Gupta"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247326020/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1247326020",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ben.grant@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ben Grant"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1562143534424
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2021",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "The College Preparatory School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "White / Caucasian | Multiracial | Other",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "It was fun last time, I wanna learn and develop project skills",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have just done the hyphen hacks last year",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Iranian",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2003-01-28",
    "changed": "2019-07-02T23:00:02Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-02T23:00:02Z",
    "email": "dzucker@thecollegepreparatoryschool.org",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247337196",
    "name": "Darius Zucker",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976802442",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2003-01-28",
      "cell_phone": "5102076449",
      "email": "dzucker@thecollegepreparatoryschool.org",
      "first_name": "Darius",
      "last_name": "Zucker",
      "name": "Darius Zucker"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247337196/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Lowell High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have attended Hyphen Hacks before and it was very fun. Last year was a very fun experience for me. I am excited to join again and make a better project.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hyphen Hacks 2018, School robotics team, and Mission Bit",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-05-11",
    "changed": "2019-07-02T23:12:29Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-02T23:12:29Z",
    "email": "joshuapan888@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247346932",
    "name": "Joshua Pan",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976808324",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-05-11",
      "cell_phone": "4157068651",
      "email": "joshuapan888@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Joshua",
      "last_name": "Pan",
      "name": "Joshua Pan"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247346932/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1247346932",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ben.grant@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ben Grant"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1562218110807
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2023",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Deeya Viradia",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Female",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "To learn from others on ideas ",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have create a AI program to detect malaria from blood sample picture",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Parents",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2005-01-01",
    "changed": "2019-07-02T23:53:15Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-02T23:53:15Z",
    "email": "23deeyav@students.harker.org",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Female",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247373048",
    "name": "Deeya Viradia",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976824298",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2005-01-01",
      "cell_phone": "4104020600",
      "email": "23deeyav@students.harker.org",
      "first_name": "Deeya",
      "last_name": "Viradia",
      "name": "Deeya Viradia"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247373048/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Sacred Heart Schools",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Black or African-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Ever since my first Hack-a-thon two years ago, I have enjoyed the challenging and innovative environment, but more so, the unpredictability of what we have do develop. Although I am not as proficient with code, I love watching the creative tools that others employ, and utilizing these techniques to better my understanding. Hypen-Hacks will provide me with a more immersive and expanded experience of a Hack-a-thon, but its abundance of mentors will encourage me to explore materials beyond my comfort zone.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I took a Computer Science course last year that was taught in Java, and have used some Swift in the past to design an app, though I have forgotten much of it. ",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website | I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-02-12",
    "changed": "2019-07-03T00:41:54Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-03T00:41:54Z",
    "email": "akagiri20@shschools.org",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247404780",
    "name": "Alan Kagiri",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976843316",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-02-12",
      "cell_phone": "16506790109",
      "email": "akagiri20@shschools.org",
      "first_name": "Alan",
      "last_name": "Kagiri",
      "name": "Alan Kagiri"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247404780/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1247404780",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ben.grant@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ben Grant"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1562115113976
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2021",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "The Athenian School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "White / Caucasian",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hyphen-Hacks has my first ever hackathon and insired me to attend more and to statr my own. I would very much like to attend for another year.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am a sublead of a FIRST robotics team, a paid intern at an electron microscope company, a student of AP computer science, and a general STEM entusiast.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends | Student leaders | MLH social media",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-11-26",
    "changed": "2019-07-03T00:48:18Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-03T00:48:18Z",
    "email": "21cjacobus@athenian.org",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247408787",
    "name": "Cooper Jacobus",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976845622",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-11-26",
      "cell_phone": "5106100933",
      "email": "21cjacobus@athenian.org",
      "first_name": "Cooper",
      "last_name": "Jacobus",
      "name": "Cooper Jacobus"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247408787/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2021",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "William Mason High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A travel reimbursement will be nice because I am coming from Ohio",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "There aren't many hackathons available in my location(Cincinnati) so I went on the MLH site and found some great hackathons.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am able to code in several languages including Java, C++, HTML, CSS, JS and etc. and now I want to use that knowledge at hackathons to create cool projects with teams.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2003-09-20",
    "changed": "2019-07-03T02:03:24Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-03T02:03:24Z",
    "email": "pchati.hack@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247454771",
    "name": "Pranav Chati",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976872487",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2003-09-20",
      "cell_phone": "(513)310-9580",
      "email": "pchati.hack@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Pranav",
      "last_name": "Chati",
      "name": "Pranav Chati"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247454771/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Elvis Bui",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "none",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am interested in attending hyphen-hacks because I want to learn and try new things that I've never done before at the hackathon, and I believe that doing these things will help me learn the skills that will help me in life.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "When I went to Hypen-Hacks last year, I didn't know what to expect from my first hackathon. I was pretty nervous about my skill level, but after the Hackathon, I had so much fun I wanted to do it again this year.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would like to borrow a laptop for this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-03-18",
    "changed": "2019-07-03T04:02:50Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-03T04:02:50Z",
    "email": "elvisbui36@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247519028",
    "name": "Elvis Bui",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976909915",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-03-18",
      "cell_phone": "9094498520",
      "email": "elvisbui36@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Elvis",
      "last_name": "Bui",
      "name": "Elvis Bui"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247519028/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1247519028",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ben.grant@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ben Grant"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1562126950541
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Lowell",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "White / Caucasian",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I enjoyed it last year",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "HH",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize you to share my application/registration information with Major League Hacking for event administration, ranking, MLH administration,and with my authorization email in-line with the MLH Privacy Policy.",
        "question_id": "23619994",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I authorize Major League Hacking to send me occasional messages about hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623007",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-03-10",
    "changed": "2019-07-03T06:55:33Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-03T06:55:33Z",
    "email": "sfr.michael@yahoo.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247579496",
    "name": "Michael Ryaboy",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "976946370",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-03-10",
      "cell_phone": "4153502921",
      "email": "sfr.michael@yahoo.com",
      "first_name": "Michael",
      "last_name": "Ryaboy",
      "name": "Michael Ryaboy"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247579496/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2023",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "San Mateo high school",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XL",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Peanuts | Tree nuts",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "none",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I want to fine tune my skills",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "BATM hacks: got second place",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Found on Eventbrite",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "NO beef/pork",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2006-09-25",
    "changed": "2019-07-03T17:13:23Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-03T17:13:23Z",
    "email": "rivaanpat@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247962084",
    "name": "Rivaan Patil",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "977186188",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2006-09-25",
      "cell_phone": "9096996641",
      "email": "rivaanpat@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Rivaan",
      "last_name": "Patil",
      "name": "Rivaan Patil"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247962084/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mission San Jose High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I enjoy going to hackathons a lot and I would love to build something at Hyphen-Hacks.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I've attended around 13-14 hackathons, have taken AP Computer Science at school and have worked as  a contractor for a company",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-11-29",
    "changed": "2019-07-03T17:54:43Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-03T17:54:43Z",
    "email": "sharmaronit009@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1247997352",
    "name": "Ronit Sharma",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "977206860",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-11-29",
      "cell_phone": "6308634213",
      "email": "sharmaronit009@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Ronit",
      "last_name": "Sharma",
      "name": "Ronit Sharma"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1247997352/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Mentor",
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "UC Berkeley",
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Undergraduate Student",
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have attended two previous hackathons, where I acted as a leader to form a team and build an app with groups of less experienced coders.",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have no official experience mentoring or judging hackathons, but I do have experience helping other teams with technical issues at the hackathons I have attended.",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I led programming on a robotics team in high school and participated in multiple other clubs where I taught peers and younger grades skills relevant to the club.",
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Java, JavaScript, Python, front-end development, design",
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2001-04-01",
    "changed": "2019-07-04T00:37:27Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-04T00:37:27Z",
    "email": "jerry.w.zhang@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1248326854",
    "name": "Jerry Zhang",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "977395332",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2001-04-01",
      "cell_phone": "4086435319",
      "email": "jerry.w.zhang@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Jerry",
      "last_name": "Zhang",
      "name": "Jerry Zhang"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1248326854/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111414717",
    "ticket_class_name": "Mentor/Judge",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1248326854",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ben.grant@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ben Grant"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1562201135291
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2021",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Sacred Heart Cathedral Preparatory ",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "White / Caucasian",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Female",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am looking to improve my coding experience outside of the school classroom.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended hackathon last year, however I was not able to attend the second day. I have completed a semester in java and a semester in python coding. Next year I am taking AP Computer Science Principles at my high school.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Teachers or school administrators",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2003-05-13",
    "changed": "2019-07-04T01:23:27Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-04T01:23:27Z",
    "email": "21npierotti@shcp.edu",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Female",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1248356634",
    "name": "Natalie Pierotti",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "977412616",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2003-05-13",
      "cell_phone": "4153416810",
      "email": "21npierotti@shcp.edu",
      "first_name": "Natalie",
      "last_name": "Pierotti",
      "name": "Natalie Pierotti"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1248356634/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Alexander Ruiz",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American | Hispanic | Multiracial",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I love hackathons, and I want to bring some of my newbie coding friends to one.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I organized Hack the Fog, an SF hackathon in March 2018, and went to two other hackathons after that. I've taken AP Computer Science, and have self taught web development (HTML/CSS/JS/ES6, React), as well as Node.JS and Python.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hack Club hackathon list",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-03-18",
    "changed": "2019-07-04T20:39:14Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-04T20:39:14Z",
    "email": "ruiz.alex0302@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1248974028",
    "name": "Alexander Ruiz",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "977781794",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-03-18",
      "cell_phone": "4158027508",
      "email": "ruiz.alex0302@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Alexander",
      "last_name": "Ruiz",
      "name": "Alexander Ruiz"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1248974028/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Rishabh Sharma",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "none",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MEET MORE DEVELOPERS AND HACK!",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have been to 10 hackathons in the last 2 weeks. I am on a running  SF hackathon spree.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Flyers/Posters | MLH website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "1999-10-02",
    "changed": "2019-07-04T23:25:20Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-04T23:25:20Z",
    "email": "rishabh.sharma9102@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1249068651",
    "name": "Rishabh Sharma",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "977836687",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "1999-10-02",
      "cell_phone": "5309085191",
      "email": "rishabh.sharma9102@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Rishabh",
      "last_name": "Sharma",
      "name": "Rishabh Sharma"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1249068651/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Justin Im",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Want a place where I can code for hours with other people who love coding without my parents putting me to bed.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Neural networks good",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-08-29",
    "changed": "2019-07-05T03:15:03Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-05T03:15:03Z",
    "email": "xthefast4x@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1249172879",
    "name": "Justin Im",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "977896873",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-08-29",
      "cell_phone": "6507870911",
      "email": "xthefast4x@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Justin",
      "last_name": "Im",
      "name": "Justin Im"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1249172879/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Lick-Wilmerding",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Multiracial",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attended last year and enjoyed the hackathon.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I try to code daily as it has been my one of my new years and summer resolutions. I have attended 3 hackathons while on this blue planet.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website | Friends | Parents | Lick-Wilmerding website | A school newspaper | Teachers or school administrators | Student leaders | Hyphen-Hacks social media | MLH social media | I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Pescatarian.",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-06-28",
    "changed": "2019-07-07T23:59:36Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-07T23:59:36Z",
    "email": "2022ejr@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1251009424",
    "name": "Ethan Rendon",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "978951363",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-06-28",
      "cell_phone": "(415) 866-1607",
      "email": "2022ejr@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Ethan",
      "last_name": "Rendon",
      "name": "Ethan Rendon"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1251009424/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": "waivers/1251009424",
    "waiverReviewedBy": {
      "email": "ronan.furuta@hyphen-hacks.com",
      "name": "Ronan Furuta"
    },
    "waiverStatus": 2,
    "waiverUploaded": 1562557368941
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Ishan Jain",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I love Hackathons!",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I attend Hackathons almost every weekend during the season. I have developed over 20+ projects.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-07-28",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T00:06:05Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T00:06:05Z",
    "email": "ishanjain42@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1251850020",
    "name": "Ishan Jain",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "979475806",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-07-28",
      "cell_phone": "5102418607",
      "email": "ishanjain42@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Ishan",
      "last_name": "Jain",
      "name": "Ishan Jain"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1251850020/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Galileo High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Female",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would like to learn more about coding and work on projects",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have been to a couple of Hackathons.  I have attended many coding classes.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Parents",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-01-14",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T19:23:03Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T19:23:03Z",
    "email": "eileen744@hotmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Female",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252557272",
    "name": "Stephanie Lee",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "979914364",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-01-14",
      "cell_phone": "4157065414",
      "email": "eileen744@hotmail.com",
      "first_name": "Stephanie",
      "last_name": "Lee",
      "name": "Stephanie Lee"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252557272/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "BASIS Independent Silicon Valley",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Female",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am interested in building a project with a team of people that have different skill sets and in attending the workshops.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have taken AP Computer Science A and have worked as a data science/bioinformatics intern in university labs. I have attended two hackathons before.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2001-11-28",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T19:36:32Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T19:36:32Z",
    "email": "aliceyeh12@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Female",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252569819",
    "name": "Alice Yeh",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "979922068",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2001-11-28",
      "cell_phone": "510-936-3268",
      "email": "aliceyeh12@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Alice",
      "last_name": "Yeh",
      "name": "Alice Yeh"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252569819/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Irvington High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Halal",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "none",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I really want to improve my programming skills. Creating is my passion and programming is my favorite medium. ",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have been to one hackathon before. I know java, python, html, css, and js",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hack Club mailing list",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-05-17",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T19:49:45Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T19:49:45Z",
    "email": "luqmanzaceria@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252582197",
    "name": "Luqman Zaceria",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "979929692",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-05-17",
      "cell_phone": "5107665554",
      "email": "luqmanzaceria@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Luqman",
      "last_name": "Zaceria",
      "name": "Luqman Zaceria"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252582197/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Design Tech",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "White / Caucasian",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I love learning and have found that hackathons have been an excellent way of doing just that. I also like meeting new people and working with teams. ",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I think I've been to around 7 or 8 hackathons now and have experience in Java, Python, Android Dev, web scraping, chrome extensions, and Unity with Oculus. ",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I got an email from Hack Club Hackathons. ",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2001-07-23",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T20:20:36Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T20:20:36Z",
    "email": "eshedd20@dtechhs.org",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252611500",
    "name": "Ethan Shedd",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "979947213",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2001-07-23",
      "cell_phone": "6502190706",
      "email": "eshedd20@dtechhs.org",
      "first_name": "Ethan",
      "last_name": "Shedd",
      "name": "Ethan Shedd"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252611500/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Junipero Serra High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hispanic",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I enjoy coding, and I would like to competitively improve my skills to help me land jobs in the future.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "APCSP, Javascript chrome extensions, websites, sketches, 2 Hackathons, won a prize at one hackathon",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Found on Eventbrite",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-02-12",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T20:35:35Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T20:35:35Z",
    "email": "davmartinetest@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252626039",
    "name": "David Martinez",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "979955581",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-02-12",
      "cell_phone": "5109622005",
      "email": "davmartinetest@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "David",
      "last_name": "Martinez",
      "name": "David Martinez"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252626039/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2021",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Dougherty Valley High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I enjoy attending hackathons frequently, and hyphen hacks seems like a good one.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I've been to roughly 13 hackathons, and gave coded since I was 10, so 6 years.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Indian",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Email",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2003-08-04",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T22:21:09Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T22:21:09Z",
    "email": "pradyungn@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252714832",
    "name": "Pradyun Narkadamilli",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980011277",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2003-08-04",
      "cell_phone": "4083682638",
      "email": "pradyungn@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Pradyun",
      "last_name": "Narkadamilli",
      "name": "Pradyun Narkadamilli"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252714832/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MSJH ",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Female",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Interested to learn technologies and try Hacktons",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None ",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2003-12-30",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T23:04:01Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T23:04:01Z",
    "email": "sahiti@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Female",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252747672",
    "name": "Sahiti Alladi",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980030910",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2003-12-30",
      "cell_phone": "+1 (510) 386-4127",
      "email": "sahiti@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Sahiti",
      "last_name": "Alladi",
      "name": "Sahiti Alladi"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252747672/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Irvington high school",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I enjoy Hackathons and have been participating since my freshman year as it gives me an opportunity to use my skills and present them. I also meet interesting mentors and students who share their experiences.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Los Altos Hack",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-02-09",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T23:15:44Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T23:15:44Z",
    "email": "shaurya0904@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252755755",
    "name": "Shaurya Srivastav",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980036044",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-02-09",
      "cell_phone": "9176501877",
      "email": "shaurya0904@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Shaurya",
      "last_name": "Srivastav",
      "name": "Shaurya Srivastav"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252755755/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2021",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Saloni Nayak",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Female",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would love to meet new people interested in tech and learn about new technologies.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have been to 5 hackathons. I have experience with html, css, JavaScript, and python.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hack Club website",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2003-06-05",
    "changed": "2019-07-09T23:59:27Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-09T23:59:27Z",
    "email": "saloni.nayak@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Female",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252787007",
    "name": "Saloni Nayak",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980055458",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2003-06-05",
      "cell_phone": "4084656479",
      "email": "saloni.nayak@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Saloni",
      "last_name": "Nayak",
      "name": "Saloni Nayak"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252787007/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Lynbrook High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I really love programming and creating cool projects. Right now, I'm especially interested in applying machine learning to the real world in interesting use cases.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "This is my life",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I've been programming since fourth grade, and I've been attending hackathons since seventh grade. I have experience in many languages and I am excellent at full-stack web development. I've taken the Deep Learning specialization by Andrew Ng on Coursera, and I have made a few machine learning projects.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Hack Club Hackathons",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-02-29",
    "changed": "2019-07-10T00:04:33Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-10T00:04:33Z",
    "email": "oliver.ni@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252790415",
    "name": "Oliver Ni",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980057626",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-02-29",
      "cell_phone": "4089133268",
      "email": "oliver.ni@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Oliver",
      "last_name": "Ni",
      "name": "Oliver Ni"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252790415/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Dougherty Valley High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "L",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "American Indian or Alaskan Native",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I want to attend more hackathons and meet more people, and work with others in programming. ",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I know some python.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A school newspaper",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-04-06",
    "changed": "2019-07-10T01:40:13Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-10T01:40:13Z",
    "email": "ishaanbansal1001@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252854119",
    "name": "Ishaan Bansal",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980097242",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-04-06",
      "cell_phone": "9259643840",
      "email": "ishaanbansal1001@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Ishaan",
      "last_name": "Bansal",
      "name": "Ishaan Bansal"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252854119/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2023",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Franklin High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I'm interested in learning new technical aspects of software development and in collaborating with others to create something fun & innovative.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I've won second place in a Hackathon at Hackerlab Midtown Sacramento and also won second place at a Hackathon at CodeforHood in Sacramento.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Found on Eventbrite",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2005-01-21",
    "changed": "2019-07-10T06:27:50Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-10T06:27:50Z",
    "email": "fishberryowners@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252990177",
    "name": "Aryan Sawant",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980180856",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2005-01-21",
      "cell_phone": "916-647-7447",
      "email": "fishberryowners@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Aryan",
      "last_name": "Sawant",
      "name": "Aryan Sawant"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252990177/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Agrim Dhingra",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "none",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I am interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks, because I have been to only 3 Hackathons before, and I would like to gain more experience.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I don't have any.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends | Found on Eventbrite",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-01-15",
    "changed": "2019-07-10T06:38:36Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-10T06:38:36Z",
    "email": "Agrimd3@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1252994185",
    "name": "Agrim Dhingra",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980183023",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-01-15",
      "cell_phone": "4087849076",
      "email": "Agrimd3@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Agrim",
      "last_name": "Dhingra",
      "name": "Agrim Dhingra"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1252994185/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Dougherty Valley High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Other",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I love attending hackathons!",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Took APCSP and AP CS A in school already. I've won 6 hackathons including Menlo and HS Hacks to name a few. I love hackathons and plan to add to that number.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yes",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH social media",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No Beef",
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-03-02",
    "changed": "2019-07-10T23:51:55Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-10T23:51:55Z",
    "email": "adheetgupta@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1253781318",
    "name": "Adheet Gupta",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "980630520",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-03-02",
      "cell_phone": "9253894690",
      "email": "adheetgupta@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Adheet",
      "last_name": "Gupta",
      "name": "Adheet Gupta"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1253781318/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2023",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vista Del Lago",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "XS",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Non-gender binary",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Learn programming and hacking",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Yellow Circle and other programming participations",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2006-05-11",
    "changed": "2019-07-11T17:08:29Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-11T17:08:29Z",
    "email": "vamba1@yahoo.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Non-gender binary",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1254418909",
    "name": "Rishabh Ambavanekar",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "981018930",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2006-05-11",
      "cell_phone": "9168711695",
      "email": "vamba1@yahoo.com",
      "first_name": "Rishabh",
      "last_name": "Ambavanekar",
      "name": "Rishabh Ambavanekar"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1254418909/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2022",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Dougherty Valley High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I would like to get better at programming by interacting and learning from others.",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I have been to several hackathons from MLH.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MLH website",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2004-08-10",
    "changed": "2019-07-11T19:12:02Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-11T19:12:02Z",
    "email": "rohanayyagari@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1254548720",
    "name": "Rohan Ayyagari",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "981092256",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2004-08-10",
      "cell_phone": "9254043496",
      "email": "rohanayyagari@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Rohan",
      "last_name": "Ayyagari",
      "name": "Rohan Ayyagari"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1254548720/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2021",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "MONTA VISTA",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "S",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Vegetarian",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Gain Hackathon experience",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Programming - Beginner\nHackathons - none",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Found on Eventbrite",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2003-09-23",
    "changed": "2019-07-12T03:54:52Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-12T03:54:52Z",
    "email": "yash.pathakji13@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1254953938",
    "name": "YASH PATHAK",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "981320987",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2003-09-23",
      "cell_phone": "4087728959",
      "email": "yash.pathakji13@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "YASH",
      "last_name": "PATHAK",
      "name": "YASH PATHAK"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1254953938/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  },
  {
    "answers": [
      {
        "answer": "2020",
        "question": "Expected Year of Graduation",
        "question_id": "23619426",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Aragon High School",
        "question": "Name of High School",
        "question_id": "23619446",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "M",
        "question": "Shirt Size",
        "question_id": "23619475",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Asian or Asian-American",
        "question": "Race/Ethnicity (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619540",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Male",
        "question": "What is your gender?",
        "question_id": "23675489",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Food Allergies (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619629",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Dietary Restrictions (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619654",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "None",
        "question": "Special Needs/Accommodations (Type \"None\" if not applicable)",
        "question_id": "23619670",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I had a great experience last year, and I want to ",
        "question": "Why are you interested in attending Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23619676",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Some amount",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with software development?",
        "question_id": "23619742",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hardware development?",
        "question_id": "23619752",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A little bit",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with hackathons?",
        "question_id": "23619776",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "A lot",
        "question": "How much experience do you have with coding in teams?",
        "question_id": "23619785",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I enjoy coding in my free time, especially on the Discord bot I made for my friends. I have attended a few hackathons in the past, but I am still relatively new to the concept. I was also an AP CS A student and was enrolled in Carnegie Mellon's National High School Game Academy for summer 2019.",
        "question": "Please give a brief description of your computer science and hackathon experiences (it's okay if you don't have any).",
        "question_id": "23619803",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Would you like to be a mentor or a judge? (See https://hyphen-hacks.com/volunteer/ for an explanation of the difference)",
        "question_id": "23623011",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "question": "What company/program are you affiliated with?",
        "question_id": "23623088",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is your position there?",
        "question_id": "23623105",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience ATTENDING hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623176",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience MENTORING or JUDGING at hackathons.",
        "question_id": "23623194",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please provide a brief description of your previous experience working with high school students in general.",
        "question_id": "23623218",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "What do you consider to be your areas of expertise (that you could help students with and/or evaluate them for)? E.g. JavaScript, machine learning, Firebase, front-end development",
        "question_id": "23623230",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "I will bring my own laptop to use at this event",
        "question": "Do you have a laptop that you can bring to Hyphen-Hacks?",
        "question_id": "23675557",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "No",
        "question": "Do you already have a team worked out?",
        "question_id": "23676865",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "Friends | I attended or was involved last year (Hyphen-Hacks 2018)",
        "question": "How did you find out about Hyphen-Hacks? (check all that apply)",
        "question_id": "23619832",
        "type": "multiple_choice"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "Please read the following: MLH Code of Conduct (https://bit.ly/2eW3gIO), MLH Contest Terms and Conditions (https://bit.ly/2wNr4rB), MLH Privacy Policy (https://mlh.io/privacy)",
        "question_id": "23619960",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "answer": "accepted",
        "question": "I understand that this is an application and my acceptance to Hyphen-Hacks has not been confirmed.",
        "question_id": "23620143",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619630",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619655",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23675490",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619541",
        "type": "text"
      },
      {
        "question": "Please specify:",
        "question_id": "23619833",
        "type": "text"
      }
    ],
    "birth_date": "2002-11-08",
    "changed": "2019-07-13T00:46:05Z",
    "checkedIn": false,
    "created": "2019-07-13T00:46:05Z",
    "email": "yuanp55@gmail.com",
    "event_id": "60509274870",
    "gender": {
      "answer": "Male",
      "question": "What is your gender?",
      "question_id": "23675489",
      "type": "multiple_choice"
    },
    "id": "1255801131",
    "name": "Philip Yuan",
    "onCampus": false,
    "order_id": "981818013",
    "profile": {
      "addresses": {},
      "birth_date": "2002-11-08",
      "cell_phone": "16507853061",
      "email": "yuanp55@gmail.com",
      "first_name": "Philip",
      "last_name": "Yuan",
      "name": "Philip Yuan"
    },
    "quantity": 1,
    "resource_uri": "https://www.eventbriteapi.com/v3/events/60509274870/attendees/1255801131/",
    "ticket_class_id": "111244170",
    "ticket_class_name": "High school Student",
    "variant_id": null,
    "waiverImage": null,
    "waiverReviewedBy": "",
    "waiverStatus": 0
  }
]